# Satyam Pandey SAP ABAP Developer

■ pandeysatyam1407@gmail.com

9260981347

Mahaveer Bower Residency, Channappanhalli, Bengaluru

77/14/1999

■ Indian

in https://www.linkedin.com/in/Satyam1407

G https://exercism.org/profiles/SatyamPandey2

### PROFILE

Having around 3 year of relevant experience in SAP ABAP with a proven track record of a company and customer satisfaction. Strength include delivering optimized design with code, good communication and Technical skill, complete multiple assignments concurrently and meet aggressive deadline, Good experience in working with project, establishing excellent communication and relationship with client.

#### PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

SAP ABAP Consultant 12/2023 - present Bengaluru, India

· Worked on Collection and Disbursement module and implemented custom mass

- · Gained good knowledge in both technical and functional areas of the components with improved program debugging skills.
- Continuously enhanced technical expertise and also provides training to colleagues.

**SAP ABAP Consultant** 10/2021 - 10/2023 Bengaluru, India

Convista Consulting Asia

- Developed and maintained ABAP programs, reports, enhancements and good knowledge of data dictionary Object.
- Provided functional and technical support to resolve customer issues and ensure smooth operations.
- · Mentored colleagues, sharing knowledge and fostering a collaborative team environment.
- · Good Experience in different function module and program debugging.

## **PROJECTS**

Empower 12/2023 - present

ABAP Consultant

- · Created Inbound services which create policy in the SAP system when the end user sends the post request.
- · Worked on a report which helps users to change standard table records and save
- · Worked on many bugs and solved tickets by debugging custom code.
- Preparing Technical Design specifications, unit test documents and ensuring timelines and deadlines are met.
- . Worked on custom workflow which create or delete lock from BP.

**NSL Project** 10/2021 - 10/2023

Techno-Functional Consultant

- · Good experience in ABAP/4 to implement flexible solutions for business requirement and also developed innovations that provide customers highly robust solutions.
- Created different correspondence type as per business requirement.

- Created exception during payment run process if item is disbursed through FQ Events Enhancement.
- Created grouping for payment run on the basis of Main Transaction and Sub Transaction using ABAP.
- Experience on Modularization using object-oriented programming methods, subroutine and FM.
- Worked with Standard FM and Wrapped it into Custom FM according to the business need.

# **SKILLS**

ABAP/RICEW
OOABAP
BAPIS, BAdIS, RFCS
SAP FS-CD

OData
Abap on Hana/S4HANA
CDS View/AMDP
RAP

### **EDUCATION**

Percentage-84%

Class XII 04/2016 - 04/2017

Sarawati Vidhya Mandir Basti, India

Percentage-79%

Class X 04/2014 - 04/2015

Sarawati Vidhya Mandir Basti, India

CGPA-9.4

# ADDITIONAL SKILL

- · Problem solved on Exercism(IDE) in ABAP.
- Solved LeetCode problem statement.
- · Blog at ABAP problem statement with solution on LinkedIn.

# LANGUAGES

• English • Hindi

## INTERESTS

• Singing • Playing cricket • Poetry

# **DECLARATION**

I hereby declare that all the facts given above are true and correct to the best of my knowledge.

Pandey, Satyam 9260981347 pandeysatyam1407@gmail.com